5min.com 2012-10-15

# 5min - Life Videopedia

5min Ltd. ("5min") is committed to protecting your privacy when you use the 5min Service, which is comprised of (i) the 5min website, currently located at www. 5min.com (and/or any successor or additional website(s) owned or operated by or for 5min); (ii) the 5min syndication network (which includes third party websites); (iii) the servers operated by or on behalf of 5min; (v) and/or any other technology and/or services that 5min provides its users. The following Privacy Policy was prepared to inform you of the information we collect about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. 

It is very important that you read and understand our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms set out in our Privacy Policy, please do not use the 5min Service. 

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will advise you that changes have been made by posting a notice on our website. Your use of the 5min Service constitutes your acceptance of the terms of our Privacy Policy, as may be amended or revised by us, and you are advised to consult our Privacy Policy regularly for any changes (revisions will be reflected by the "last update" notation below). 

If you have any questions regarding 5min's policies or practices relating to privacy, please direct them to [privacy@5min.com](mailto:privacy@5min.com)

This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 15, 2011. 

Collection and Use of Information 

While using the 5min Service you may, among other things, gather information on our website, publish your own content, subscribe to one of our services. In doing so, we may collect certain information about you. 

We may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding use of the 5min Service, like the number of users and frequency and manner of usage of the 5min Service. We may also collect aggregated information regarding the use of our subscription-based service network, such as the extent to which certain features are used. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of our user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. We use this information to better understanding how the 5min Service is used, and to improve the online experience of our users. This information is not used in a way that will personally identify you. 

Similarly, we may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on our website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that our website places onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies identify your computer hard drive so that we can recognize you the next time you visit us. We use cookies to collect and store some information about you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website. We use this information to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. In the same manner, we may also engage third parties to monitor the usage of the 5min Service. These third parties may use cookies and web beacons (which collect non-personally identifiable information regarding user behavior on our website) to collect such information, which is also used to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. You may disable cookies by following directions on your web browser. Disabling cookies also disables web beacons. You should be aware, however, that by disabling cookies you may be unable to access certain services and features of the 5min Service. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements viewed or clicked) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out page.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

We may collect personally identifiable information from you when you seek access to certain portions of the 5min Service, publish content, and/or register for our services. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, physical and e-mail addresses, phone and/or fax numbers, Internet address, type of computer or other payment information, as well as your preferences and usage patterns. This information may be used to fulfill your requests for services, to communicate with you about your account, to support your online activities, to respond to your questions, to customize your experience and to customize the content or features of the 5min Service. We may use your personally identifiable information to notify you of changes to the 5min Service, Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy. We may also use your personally identifiable information to personalize your interactive experience on the 5min Service. For example, if you have given us permission, we may use your information to inform you of other products or services that you may find valuable. We may also use the information you provide to make improvements that better serve our users' needs. 

If you prefer not to receive information about additional products and services that we think you may be interested in, you can choose not to receive this information by opting-out when given the opportunity at the point we ask you for your contact information. 

Disclosure of Information 

We may share aggregated statistical information about users of the 5min Service with third-parties, including our distributors, vendors, actual and potential customers and third-parties that offer products or services for use with the 5min Service. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

5min will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties, with the following exceptions: 

  1. As necessary to third parties who perform services for us in operating and marketing the 5min Service, included but not limited to the monitoring of user behavior on our website and the processing of payments for products or services. 
  2. If you obtain the 5min Client bundled with product(s) from a third-party company, we may share some of your personally identifiable information with that company. If we share your personally identifiable information with such a company, that company's privacy policy will govern its use of your information. 
  3. We may be obliged or deem it necessary or appropriate to disclose your information in certain special situations. These situations include: in response to legal process such as a court order or subpoena; to prevent or combat fraud; enforcement of our Terms of Use; and protection of the rights, property or safety of 5min, our users or others. 
  4. We may disclose your information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of our company and to parents, subsidiaries or affiliates of 5min. 

Security 

5min is committed to taking appropriate measures to protect your privacy against unauthorized disclosures. 5min uses a variety of secure techniques designed to protect your information. 

While we have implemented safeguards, you should be aware that Internet security technology rapidly changes. As such, we cannot guarantee that the safeguards we employ today can protect your personal information from the threats of tomorrow, or that our security measures are failsafe and not subject to circumvention or unauthorized intrusion. You should also be aware that, despite our best efforts, factors beyond our control may result in disclosure of data. 

Third-Party Links 

Portions of the 5min Service may contain links to other third party websites that you may access. These other sites have their own privacy policies, and you should review those policies before following those links. We cannot control the information disclosed at these third-party sites or how that information is used. 

Young Children 

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. To best protect your child's privacy, we suggest that you carefully supervise your child's access to the Internet and our website. For more information on how to protect your child's privacy, you can visit the Federal Trade Commission's Kidzprivacy page, accessible via [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/)

Notice for Users Outside of the United States 

You should be aware that the United States and other countries have not harmonized their privacy regulations. Because the 5min Service is intended specifically for users in the United States, we have written our Privacy Policy to satisfy United States regulations. By using the 5min Service, you agree to the level of privacy protection set out in our Privacy Policy. 

Contact Information for 5min 

You can contact us at: 

5min Media  
770 Broadway, 5th floor  
New York, NY, 10003 

You may also use the [Contact Us](http://www.5min.com/Info/ContactUs.aspx) page
